Would you like to come to Japan?
>> Yeah. Would you like to come to
Japan? Sorry to interrupt.
>> What the heck? This might be one of the
top meals I've ever had in my life.
I feel quiet.
>> I'm a never-ending crazy YouTuber.
>> I'm in Tokyo, Japan, and today I'm only
taking you to places recommended by
locals. One of my followers said that I
should go to the Tokyo Metropolitan
Government Building because they have
free observation decks. That's amazing.
I feel like observation decks usually
cost an arm and a leg, so this is a
great pro tip. I'm hoping to get a good
view of the city before it rains. Let's
go.
I made it. Wow, it's so tall. I have to
go up to the 45th floor.
My ears [music] were popping on the
elevator.
It's a little bit foggy today, but I
still got a great view of the skyline. I
definitely think it's worth checking
this place out, especially because it's
completely free, which is crazy. Thank
you for the excellent recommendation.
I'm in Asakusa because someone
recommended a very traditional Japanese
restaurant in this area. They serve
something called loach fish. I've never
heard of it before, but I'm excited to
get out of my comfort zone and try
something completely new. Wow. This
wooden building on the corner is the
restaurant. It looks very old and
traditional. So cool.
Hello. Just one person? Is it okay?
>> Okay.
>> Do you to sit at a table or a Japanese
style?
>> Uh maybe Japanese style. Should I put my
shoes here? Take my shoes off?
Okay.
I'm sitting cross-legged on the floor,
Japanese style, and look at the view out
the window. Gorgeous.
This is the loach. I got it without
bones and without the head. I think this
is tofu and konjac. It kind of looks
like a popsicle, though.
They keep bringing more and more food
out.
This is the perfect meal for a rainy
day.
It smells so good.
This is what it looks like. They
recommend dipping it in some pepper, and
they also have sauce.
It's very soft and mild. Not super fishy
or anything. I like it.
Ah, oh.
Okay. Okay, thank you. She just dumped a
bunch of sauce on it, so I bet it's
going to be even tastier now.
So good.
Ooh,
this is so sweet. It tastes like
dessert. It's so yummy.
Wow, that place was an absolute gem.
They had an English menu, so I'm sure
they do get some tourists, but when I
was there, I was the only non-Japanese
person. It's definitely somewhere I
couldn't have found on my own. Last
night, I went to a sake bar, and the
bartender said that her favorite sweet
potato cake is also in this area, so I'm
on the hunt for it now. Look how dark
the sky is. I feel like it's going to
downpour any minute now, but I came
prepared today. I have an umbrella with
me. Oh my gosh, it's pouring right now.
I don't know what anything is, but I'm
going [music] to go with my heart on
this one.
I'm going to get two of these. I hope
this is right. Wow, it looks like jelly.
So interesting.
Mmm,
it has that really strong sweet potato
flavor. It's kind of like sweet potato
paste. [music] I like it.
I'm heading to my next [music] stop,
Bongen Coffee in Gangnam. Let's go.
What's most popular?
>> Our recommendation is this one, Bongen
Latte Rich Premium. This one is super
strong. It's espresso latte.
>> Oh.
>> If you like espresso, we recommend this.
>> Okay, it'll give me some energy.
>> [laughter]
>> Dark roast?
Dark roast is nutty and fruity.
>> I usually go for dark roast.
>> House blend?
>> House blend? Okay, I'll go for the dark
roast, please. I got a latte from Bongen
Coffee. It's one of the bougiest coffee
shops I've ever been to. I think it cost
about eight US dollars. Not cheap, but
it looks really good and high quality,
so let's try it.
Mmm, that's a well-made latte. It's
quite strong and bitter, like she said
it would be, but that's how I like my
coffee.
I was [snorts] told to come to
Kichijoji, so that's where I am now. I
made a dinner reservation in the area
for tonight, but I have some time to
kill, so I'm just going to kind of look
around and explore the area. I want to
see what this neighborhood has to offer.
I randomly came across this puppy cafe
and I want to check it out. Let's go.
Hi.
So cute. Oh my god.
>> [laughter]
>> They love the treats. They can smell it.
Be patient. Be patient.
He was aggressive. Calm down. Calm down.
He's devouring this. Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, down. Down. All right, you're cute.
You get the last bite.
Okay, I made a friend. He's so cute.
Hi.
He just said we're kids.
Okay, he's my favorite. He's on my lap.
I might have to take him home.
Someone broke out the treats and he
left.
That was so fun. I got my puppy fix. The
only problem is I want to take them all
home with me. Ugh, I want a dog so bad.
Maybe one day.
I was excited because I made the
reservation like 2 days ago. Yeah, the
one in Shibuya is like completely
booked. I heard it's almost impossible
to get, so. Wow, just a walk-up then.
I think so, yeah.
They say to take [music] the first bite
as is without any sauce or condiments.
What in the heck? That's so juicy. It's
so flavorful, too, even without any
sauce.
Dude, it looks so plain and simple, but
it's a total flavor bomb. It's really
amazing.
Hands down, this is my favorite thing
I've gluten in Tokyo so far.
I added radish and ponzu sauce. I'm
trying to eat slowly and [music] savor
it.
I'm eating the egg. I'm dipping the
patty into the egg mixture.
This might be one of the top meals I've
ever had [music] in my life. I'm not
being dramatic. It's that good.
I got to walk this off. I have a food
baby now.
So good, though, really. This place is
viral for a reason. We like this area.
It's a nice place to walk around. It
seems kind of trendy and hipster here.
It's quiet, but there's a lot of local
stores here, which is really cool. I
wish that we had had better weather,
could have explored more.
>> [laughter]
>> They were funny. That was a cool
interaction.
Packed, hey?
>> [laughter]
>> We're with our friend KJ right now. We
first met him in California and now we
found him in Tokyo and he's showing us
all the best local bars.
>> Hey guys.
>> [crying]
[laughter]
>> I didn't know it was like so uncommon to
eat.
>> [laughter]
>> Crazy YouTuber.
>> You know I did.
Tofu.
Okay, that's next level.
>> Oh, she recently had live octopus.
>> True. [music]
I did. Yeah.
That was fun.
>> [laughter]